Gross, James Additional NLRB Research Files /4166
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
James Gross Additional NLRB Research Files
1947-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gross, James
/4166
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3108905
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 09, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 03, 2016
Biographical / Historical
James Gross (1933-) was raised near Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. He graduated from La Salle University with a Bachelor of Science in 1956. Gross received his Ph.D. from the University of Wisconsin in 1962.
He taught as an assistant professor at Holy Cross College from 1960 to 1966 before joining the faculty at Cornell. He was named an associate professor in 1968 and a full professor in 1975.
Gross's three-volume history of the National Labor Relations Board has been called both authoritative and exhaustive. The Reshaping of the National Labor Relations Board: National Labor Policy in Transition, 1937-1947, the second volume of his trilogy, won the Philip Taft Labor History Book Award in 1983.
He is a member of the National Academy of Arbitrators, the American Arbitration Associaiton, and the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service.
Gross received a grant from the National Endowment for the Humanities, and in 2007 was Fulbright Visiting Research Chair in Corporate Social Responsibility at McGill University in Canada.
Biographical / Historical
NLRB 1935-2010
The National Labor Relations Board is proud of its 75-year history of enforcing the National Labor Relations Act, the primary law governing relations between employers and employees in the private sector. On July 5, 1935, President Franklin Roosevelt signed the Act into law, stating that the law sought to achieve "common justice and economic advance." Starting in the Great Depression and continuing through World War II and the economic growth and challenges that followed, the NLRB has worked to guarantee the rights of employees to bargain collectively, if they choose to do so.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4057: James Gross NLRB Files /4057 AV: James Gross NLRB Audiocassettes /4057 P: James Gross NLRB Photographs /4124: James Gross Papers, Additional NLRB Research Files /4232: James Gross Collection of NLRB 60th Annual Conference Files /4186: James Gross Additional Research Files /4190: James Gross Additional Research Files 5697: James A. Gross Arbitration Files 5959: James Gross Additional Arbitration Files /4079: James Gross Additional Files /4166 AV: James Gross Additional NLRB Research Audio-Visual Materials
Gross, James A., 1933-; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations-- Faculty; United States. National Labor Relations Board
3108905
- Oral History Tapes, Vol. 3: Miscellaneous tape recordings of oral history interviews.; Copies of Journal Articles.. (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Law Review Articles, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Law Review Articles, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Law Review Articles, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NLRB Representation Disputes, 1958-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - NLRB and Race, Discrimination, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Protection of Individual's Rights Articles, 1958-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Articles on Secondary Boycott and Hot- Cargo Provisions, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Labor No Man's Land: Federal and State Jurisdiction, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondences, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Daily Labor Reports and Miscellaneous Correspondences Related to NLRB, 1961-1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Addresses by Frank McCulloch and William Feldesman, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - NLRB Press Releases, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Recent Trends, Developments and Labor Law Cases, 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - NLRA Developments, Interpretations and Related Acts, 1959-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Articles on the History and Genesis of the NLRA and Labor Law, 1959-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Oral History-Transcripts Marked copies.. (Box 2)
  - Farmer, Guy Interview (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Interview Notes, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Kleiler, Frank Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kleeb, Howard Interview, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Jenkins, Howard Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Kammholz, Theophil Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Higgins, John Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Herzog, Paul Interview, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Herzog, Paul M. Interview and Correspondence, 1945-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Gordon, H. Stephen Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Miller, Thomas W. Jr. Interview, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - NLRB 50th Anniversary Conference, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - McCulloch, Frank Interview (Part 1), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Fanning, John Interview, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Coppock, Shelly: Management Opposition to the NLRB During the 1960s, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Come, Norton Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Brown, Gerald Interview, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bott, George Interview, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bott, George Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Barghausen, Meta Interview, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Baisinger, William Interview, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Asher, Lester Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Feldesman, William Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pollitt, Daniel H. Interview, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Davidson, Warren Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Zagoria, Sam Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Winkler, Ralph Interview, 1975-1988 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Welles, Melvin Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Walsh, Michael F. Interview, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Truesdale, John Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Subrin, Berton Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Strauss, Stanley R. Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Reilly, Gerald Interview, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Mallet- Provost, Marcel Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Pucinski, Roman Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - DeSio, Joseph Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ordman, Arnold Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - O'Connell, Francis A. Interview, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Nash, Peter Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Miller, Ed Interview (Carbon Copy), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - McGuiness, Kenneth Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - McCulloch, Frank Interview (Copy), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - McCulloch, Frank Interview (Carbon Copy), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - McCulloch, Frank Interview (Part 3), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - McCulloch, Frank Interview (Part 2), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Ranter, Mozart Interview, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- NLRB 1970's: Some Hagley Museum-Some National Archives; (Notes & photocopies). (Box 3)
  - Misc. Correspondence, Memoranda, Press Releases and Daily Labor Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Articles and Addresses, 1962-1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chamber Activity Against NLRB, 1962-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Articles Regarding NLRB, 1960-1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A Comparison of Democrat and Republican Party Platforms- 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NLRB Press Releases, 1960-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Daily and Monthly Labor Reports, 1960-1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings and Articles, 1963-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Misc. Publications, Articles and Memoranda, 1958-1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Misc. Letters, Notes, Articles, and Memoranda, 1977-1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Opinion Research Corporation, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hearings before Subcommittee on Labor on H.R. 7152 of the 92nd Congress to Amend the National Labor Relations Act, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NULL (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Misc. Memoranda, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bulletins Published by the NLRB, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Leiserson Letters Re: Functions of the Division of Economic Research and Acknowledgements, 1936-1940 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NLRB Press Releases, 1961-1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Misc. Articles, Reports, Letters, and Memos, 1947-1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Memoranda, Letters, and Congressional Reports, 1936-1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Congressional Records (1960) and Memoranda (1970-1973), 1960-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - U.S. Government Memoranda, 1970-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Misc. Letters, Memoranda, Articles, and Press Releases, 1946-1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - The Labor Lawyer, Hearings on H.R. 1236 ('73) and Labor Relations Committee Members ('70-'78), 1970-1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Press Releases and Articles, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Articles on Current Events Regarding the NLRB, 1969-1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- NLRB 1960's: Congressional Record-Some Hagley Museum-Some Eisenhower Library; Notes & photocopies.. (Box 4)
  - Misc. NLRB and News Reports, 1976-1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chamber of Commerce Labor Relations Committee 1960s, 1959-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 89th Congress 1st Session, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 88th Congress 2nd Session, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Congressional Record, house and Senate- 88th Congress 1st Session, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 87th Congress 2nd Session, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 89th Congress 1st Session, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Labor Law Reform, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 89th Congress 2nd Session, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Courts Post 1965, 1953-1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - NLRB Cases and Related Papers, 1964-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - NLRB Cases, 1968-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ervin Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - LLSG Makeup, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board Member Jenkins, NLRB and Notes, 1957-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Interview Material and Congressional Record Appendix ('48), 1948-1990 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - NLRB Correspondences, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Somers, A. Norman Interview, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Interview Notes and Set-up, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Blue Ribbon Committee and Daily Labor Reports, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Press Releases and Browne and Sachs Article, 1977-1982 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases and Daily Labor Reports, 1972-1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Congressman Thompson- NLRB, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Monthly Labor Review ('88) and Interview Materials ('50-'78), 1950-1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Interview Notepads, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Office of the General Council- NLB, 1960-1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 91st Congress 2nd Session, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 91st Congress 1st Session, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 90th Congress 2nd Session, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 90th Congress 1st Session, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Congressional Record, House and Senate- 89th Congress 2nd Session, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - NLRB Decisions and Press Releases, 1961-1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- NLRB Late 1950's and Early 1960's: National Archives-Eisenhower Library-Lyndon B. Johnson Library-John F. Kennedy Library-New York Times Index and Chronology for 1950's; Photocopies.. (Box 5)
  - Regional Information Program to Improve Communications Between Labor and Management, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1958-1962 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Hearings Before Committee on Government Operations (86th Congress) on Selective Certification methods of Appointing Hearing Examiners, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 25th Annual Report of the NLRB, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 24th Annual Report of the NLRB and Report on Operations, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 23rd Annual Report of the NLRB, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1946-1959 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - News and Press Releases, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Memos, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rothman Administration and Caseload, 1948-1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "The Duty to Bargain in a Non-Compulsory Society" Remarks by Stewart Rothman, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - News, Press Releases, DLR, 1965-1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - News, DLRs and Reports, 1949-1961 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence and Press Releases, and Notes, 1950-1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "Four Ways to Reduce Administrative Delay" Remarks by Stewart Rothman, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Hearings Before the Committee on Education and Labor (85th Congress) on the NLRA, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Articles, and DLR, 1958-1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - DLR, News, and Correspondence, 1959-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Plan 5- Pucinski, Hzgs ('61), Interview Notes and Letters, 1957-1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - News, Correspondence, and Reports, 1949-1953 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Daily Labor Reports, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - News, Duke Law Review and Speech by Frank W. McCulloch, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Monthly and Daily Labor Reports, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Articles Concerning NLRB, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Election Campaign Themes, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Monthly Summary of Activities and Decisions of the NLRB, 1962-1966 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - News, DLRs, Notes and Press Releases, 1958-1967 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - New York Times Index ('55-'59), 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - New York Times Chronology ('55-'59), 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Reports, News, and DLR, 1959-1962 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Statement by the AFL-CIO Executive Council on NLRB Budget, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - "An Enemy of the People" A Play in Five Acts (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Index to Legal Periodicals, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NLRB Biographies and News, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hearing Before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare (85th Congress) on Philip Ray Rodgers' Nomination to NLRB, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Address by Boyd Leedom, Correspondences and Press Releases of NLB, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - News and Harvard Law Review, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Correspondences, Reports, DLR, and Reviews, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, Reports, and Law Reviews, 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence and DLR, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "An Outline of Law and Procedure in Representation Cases", 1962 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Recommendations for Labor Relations Legislation Made by President Eisenhower, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- NLRB: National Archives-Truman Library; Documents from 1947-Late 1950's. (Box 6)
  - Chapter 3: Congressional Records- House and Senate, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 1: Letters and Memoranda, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 4: Decisions of National Labor Relations Board, 1948-1952 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 4: News Clippings, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 4: Congressional Record- Senate, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 3: News Clippings and Press Releases, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 3: News Clippings and Press Releases, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 3: Notes on Research (1988?) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 3: Report of the Joint Committee on Labor- Management Relations, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 3: Hearing before Committee on Labor and Public Welfare on Confirmation of Nominees for NLRB, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 4: Hearings before the Subcommittees of the Committee on Education and Labor and of the Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 3: Decisions of the NLRB and Tennessee Law Review: The Taft- Hartley Act- Denham, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 4: Correspondence and Letters, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 3: Misc. Reports, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 2: Conference- Provisions of the Taft- Hartley Act by The American Federation of Labor, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 2: Conference- Provisions of the Taft- Hartley Act by The American Federation of Labor, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 2: Misc. Reports, Journals, and Broadcasts, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 2: Congressional Records- Senate, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 2: News Clippings, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 2: Letters and Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 1: Veto Message of the Taft- Hartley Act, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 1: Misc. Statements, Reports, and Recommendations (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 1: News Clippings, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 3: Letters and Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 5: News Clippings, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Chapter 5: Congressional Records- House and Senate, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Chapter 5: Report Approving Reorganization Plan No. 5 of 1961 by Mr. Dawson of the Committee on Government Operations (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Chapter 5: Report on Organization of the NLRB by the Advisory Panel on Labor- Management Relations Law, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Chapter 5: Hearing Before Committee on Labor and Public Welfare on Nomination of Stuart Rothman and Edwin Price, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Chapter 5: Report of the Subcommittee on National elations Board on Administration of the Labor- Management Relations Act by the NLRB, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Chapter 5: Hearings Before the Committee on Government Operations (US House and Senate) on Reorganization Plan No. 5 of 1961 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Chapter 5: Letters and Memoranda, 1949-1961 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Chapter 5: Daily Labor Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Chapter 5: News Clippings and Press Releases, 1948-1962 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Chapter 4: Twelfth Intermediate Report of the Committee on Expenditures in the Executive Departments, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 5: University Law Reviews and Document Reproduction Request Document (1988), 1960-1988 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - NULL (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Chapter 5: News Clippings, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Chapter 5: Report of the Joint Committee on Labor- Management Relations, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Chapter 5: National Labor Relations Act of 1949: Report by Mr. Thomas of Utah (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Chapter 5: National Labor Relations Act of 1949: Minority Views (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Chapter 5: Statements, Reports, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Chapter 5: Letters, Memoranda, and Press Releases of Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Chapter 4: Hearings Before the Joint Committee on Labor- Management Relations on the Operation of the Labor- Management Relations Act, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Chapter 4: Hearings Before the Joint Committee on Labor- Management Relations on the Operation of the Labor- Management Relations Act, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Chapter 4: University Law Review Articles, 1948-1952 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Chapter 4: Notes on Research (1988?) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Chapter 5: Misc. Reports, Articles, and More, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- NLRB Inventories: Truman Library-Kennedy Library-George Meany Memorial Archives-Hagley Museum-Johnson Library-Stanley Diary (Eisenhower Library)-New York Times Index-Index to Legal Periodicals-NLRB Press Release List-Release Guide List to 1983.. (Box 7)
  - Reader's Guide to Periodical Literature, 1949-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Archives of NAM, Accession 1411 Series I, Subject Files 100-A through 100-ZZ; 200-A, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Appendix I to Acc. 1411 of NAM Archive, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Eisenhower Library, Copy of Journal Entries Regarding Labor Laws, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Eisenhower Library, Copy of Journal Entries Regarding Labor Laws, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ct. Law Review Articles List (w/ Abstracts and Notes) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Harvard Law Review Vol. 96, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Harvard Law Review Vol. 78, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Index to Legal Periodicals, Subjects and Authors, 1952-1982 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "Labor Law" Periodical Search Continued (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Labor law" Entries in Index to Legal Periodicals, 1981-1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Document Reproduction Requests and Orders, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Reader's Guide to Periodical Literature, 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - New York Times Index and Articles, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Article and monthly Summaries of the Activity of the NLRB, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - DLR, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - News and Press Releases, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - New York Times Chronology and Index, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New York Times Articles, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - New York Times Articles, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - New York Times Index and Articles, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - New York Times Index and Articles, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - New York Times Index and Articles, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - New York Times Indices ('47-'54), 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NLRB Inventories: Truman Library-Kennedy Library-George Meany Memorial Archives-Hagley Museum-Johnson Library-Stanley Diary (Eisenhower Library)-New York Times Index-Index to Legal Periodicals-NLRB Press Release List-Release Guide List to 1983.. (Box 8)
  - Letters and Memoranda, 1948-1962 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Selected NLRB Cases Requested by Professor Gross (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NLRB Anniversary Conference, A Symposium of the NLRA, News Articles, and Board Decision and Orders, 1950-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee Law Review Vol. 23: "The NLRB: Its Past, Present, and Future" -Farmer, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Law Review Vol. 39: "The Evolution of the 'Duty to Bargain' Concept in American Law" -Smith, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland State Law Review: "Industrial Democracy: America's Unfulfilled Promise" -Summers, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - George Washington Law Review: "Later History and Development of the NLRB" -Rodgers, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Memoranda, and Speeches, 1958-1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings and Press Releases, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Daily Labor Repots, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Articles and Analysis, 1962-1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Document Reproduction Requests and Related Documents, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Interview Notes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Research Materials and Notes (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - News Clippings and Chronology- 1965 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Articles and Statements, 1971-1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Misc. NY Times Indices, Indices to Legal Periodicals, Subject and Author and NYT Chronology ('60), 1946-1970 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Official Papers and Reports, Timeline of NLRB Members (1980s), 1947-1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 13th- 20th Annual Repot, NLRB- Notes, 1948-1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1957 Releases (NLRB Press?) (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Special Releases- Beginning with Taft- Hartley Act: R-1 through R-515, 1947-1955 (Box 8, Folder 21)